[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What part of the human being is the shen according to traditional Chinese medicine?", "correct_answer": "Soul", "incorrect_answers": ["Breath", "Bodily fluids", "Heart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie I Am Sam, this actress plays Rita Harrison, the pro bono attorney who decides to be Sams lawyer?", "correct_answer": "Michelle Pfeiffer", "incorrect_answers": ["Ahsley Judd", "Jodie Foster", "Nicole Kidman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Turtles can stick out their tongues to catch food.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In a galaxy far, far away, I killed a twenty foot, drooling monster with a door. Who am I?", "correct_answer": "Luke Skywalker", "incorrect_answers": ["Beowolf", "The Incredible Hulk", "Aragorn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of meat is used for the preparation of the traditional Native American soup called Pira caldo?", "correct_answer": "Fish", "incorrect_answers": ["Llama", "Guinea pig", "Duck"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did the color burnt orange get its name?", "correct_answer": "1915", "incorrect_answers": ["1920", "1913", "1923"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jason Voorhees, the main character in Friday the 13th series puts on a mask to hide his horrible face in which movie?", "correct_answer": "Friday the 13th Part 3", "incorrect_answers": ["Friday the 13th Part 2", "Friday the 13th Part VI: Jason Lives", "Friday the 13th: A New Beginning"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where do most of the scenes in the Halloween II movie take place?", "correct_answer": "hospital", "incorrect_answers": ["school", "shopping mall", "church"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1860 South Carolina became the first state to secede from the Union.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The word zombie is never used in any of the Resident Evil movies.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After roasting, one pound (0.5 kg) of green coffee beans yields how much dried coffee?", "correct_answer": "Slightly less than one pound / 0.5 kg", "incorrect_answers": ["Slightly more than one pound / 0.5 kg", "Almost two pounds / 1 kg", "One pound / 0.5 kg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is the odd one out?", "correct_answer": "Jonquil", "incorrect_answers": ["Carnelian", "Beryl", "Jasper"]}]